Library. University Librarian. Administrative files UARC.0377
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Library Plans for 1980's., 890790 (Box 361, Folder 22)
- Economic Impact report., 1990.; 890789 (Box 361, Folder 23)
- Mindlin., 1992.; 890788 (Box 361, Folder 24)
- MCLS., 890787 (Box 361, Folder 25)
- MRAP (Management Review and Analysis Program/UCLA Library 1974-1977 - final report copy 1., 890786 (Box 361, Folder 26-27)
- Long Range Development Plan (UCLA)., 1989-1990.; 890785 (Box 361, Folder 28)
- GSLIS (Graduate School of Library and information Science) - Advisory Council., 1991-1992.; 890784 (Box 361, Folder 29)
- Shaver Company report [private sector support]., 1989.; 890783 (Box 361, Folder 30)
- Miscellaneous files from the Ed[ucation]/Psych[ology] Library., 890782 (Box 362, Folder 1)
  Includes UCLA slide tape "How to Use the ERIC System"; also Jim Cox files on copyright, including theses and dissertations.
- Microfilm only: brieflisted, the "2 millions" [i. e. seven digit numbers starting with 2] many "Hebraica;" also dissertations on microfilm with numbers like 05467 or 20280, 890781 (Box 363, Folder 1)
  COLLECTION CONTAINS AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audiovisual materials in this collection will require assessment and possible digitization for safe access. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
- Education Psychology (EdPsych) Library Annual Reports, 1973-1981; 1988-1989; 890100 (Box 364, Folder 1-9)
- University Librarian Reports to the Chancellor, 1964-1973; 890099 (Box 364, Folder 10)
- Graduate School of Education Advisory Committee to Ed Psych Library, 1985-1991; 890098 (Box 364, Folder 11)
- Psychology Department/Ed Psych Library, 1984; 890097 (Box 364, Folder 12)
- TESL/Ed Psych Library, 1988-1990; 890096 (Box 364, Folder 13)
- Monographic Processing Procedures, no date; 890095 (Box 364, Folder 14-15)
- Acquisitions/Collection Development/Norman Dudley, 1965-1982; 890094 (Box 365, Folder 1-4)
- Latin American Annual Reports, 1972-1973; 1975-1977; 1979-1980; 890093 (Box 365, Folder 6)
- Latin American Bibliographer Acquisitions and Collection Development, 1966-1981; 890092 (Box 365, Folder 7-8)
- Library Council, 1968-1975; 890091 (Box 365, Folder 9-10)
- Acquisitions Notes of Robert Vosper, 1946-1952; 890088 (Box 366, Folder 1)
- Clark Library Annual Reports, 1946-1966; 890087 (Box 366, Folder 2)
- Department Heads Meetings Minutes, 1951-1966; 890086 (Box 366, Folder 3-5)
- Librarian's Collection Development Letters to Faculty, 1942-1962; 890085 (Box 366, Folder 6)
- Library Committee to the Academic Senate Annual Reports, 1942-1962; 890084 (Box 366, Folder 7)
- Library Policies, 1955; 890083 (Box 366, Folder 8)
- Reference Department, 1947-1961; 890082 (Box 366, Folder 9)
- University Librarian Annual Reports to the Chancellor, 1957-1966; 890081 (Box 366, Folder 10)
- University of California (UC) Size of the Libraries, 1949-1975; 890080 (Box 366, Folder 11)
- UCLA Size of Libraries, 1954-1976; 890079 (Box 366, Folder 12)
- Buildings (Tom Ortiz), 1970-1975; 890078 (Box 367, Folder 1-34)
- Ed Psych LibraryAcquisitions, 1985-1989; 890077 (Box 368, Folder 1)
- Ed Psych Library Annual Reports, 1966-1990; 890076 (Box 368, Folder 2-9)
- Ed Psych Library Circulation Resources, 1982-1992.; 890074 (Box 368, Folder 10)
- Ed Psych Library Facility Improvement, 1967-1986; 890073 (Box 368, Folder 11)
- Library Staffing, 1967-1968; 890072 (Box 369, Folder 1)
- Public Catalog Committee and Working Group on Public Catalogs Final Report, 1975-1976; 890071 (Box 369, Folder 2-3)
- Public Services Manual, 1987; 890070 (Box 369, Folder 4)
- UCLA Librarians Association, 1969; 890069 (Box 369, Folder 5)
- Library Staff Association Committee Records, 1961-1984; 890068 (Box 370, Folder 1-4)
- Microfilm of accession records Reel 1 (27,784-30,999) to Reel 42 (to 701,252); then through 2,063,711); Missing: reels 24, 28., n.d.; 890780; 57 reels total (Box 371)
- Ad Hoc Committee on Privacy and Retention of Library Records, 1988; 890752 (Box 372, Folder 1)
- Barker, Nicolas, 1987-1989; 890765 (Box 372, Folder 2)
- Combined Art and Architecture and Urban Planning Library (School of Arts and Architecture: Fine Arts Libraries), 1988; 890771 (Box 372, Folder 3)
- Disabilities, c. 1992; 890740 (Box 372, Folder 4)
- Disaster preparedness, 1990; 890739 (Box 372, Folder 5)
- EDUCOM Project Delta, 1992; 890770 (Box 372, Folder 6)
- Engineering and Mathematical Sciences Library (EMS), 1989-1993; 890777 (Box 372, Folder 7)
- Engineering Research Center Information Center, 1990; 890772 (Box 372, Folder 8)
- Faculty Research Database, 1993; 890767 (Box 372, Folder 9)
- Faculty Rewards, Universitywide Task Force on, report, 1991; 890769 (Box 372, Folder 10)
- Foreign Language Instruction, 1992; 890766 (Box 372, Folder 11)
- LAUC-LA, 1991-1993; 890738; 2 folders (Box 372, Folder 12)
- Oral History Program Faculty Advisory Committee, 1992-1994; 890736 (Box 372, Folder 13)
- ORION, 1989-1993; 890764; Includes Campus Databases, Expres fund, Income, Priorities, Projects, Task lists, and User Services Annual reports. (Box 372, Folder 14-20)
- Pacific Bell, 1992; 890757 (Box 372, Folder 21)
- Parking, 1989-1991; 890756 (Box 372, Folder 22)
- Physical Sciences and Technology Libraries, 1988-1993; 890755 (Box 372, Folder 23)
- Powell Library Space Planning, 1991-1994; 890754 (Box 372, Folder 24)
- Preservation, 1988-1991; 890753 (Box 372, Folder 25)
- Professional Schools Restructuring Initiative, 1993 June; 890751 (Box 372, Folder 26)
- Public Information Office/publicity, 1989-1993; 890750 (Box 372, Folder 27)
- Public Services Council, 1991 (Box 372, Folder 28)
- Reagan Presidential Library, 1990; 890748 (Box 372, Folder 29)
- Rebuild L.A., 1992; 890747 (Box 372, Folder 30)
- Reference Department, 1990-1991; 890746 (Box 372, Folder 31)
- Reports on Academic and Instructional Computing, University of California, 1986 and 1989; 890743 (Box 372, Folder 32)
- Reprographic Services, 1990-1993; 890745 (Box 372, Folder 33)
- Research Libraries Group, 1991-1992; 890742 (Box 372, Folder 34)
- Reserves, 1992; 890741 (Box 372, Folder 35)
- Rich, Andrea-Gloria Werner memos, 1989-1991; 890768 (Box 372, Folder 36)
- Senate Concurrent Resolution 43 (SCR43)--Diversity and Multiculturality, 1989; 890779 (Box 372, Folder 37)
- Shared Collections and Access Program, 1990; 890778 (Box 372, Folder 38)
- Southern Regional Library Facility Board, 1989-1993; 890776 (Box 372, Folder 39-44)
- Audio (College, 1966 and Ed/Psych 1972)., 890735 (Box 373, Folder 1)
- Main Library [Research Library] Alteration, step 2., 1964.; 890734 (Box 373, Folder 2)
- College Library Alterations step 2., 1966.; 890733 (Box 373, Folder 3)
- Library floorplans., c. 1960-1967.; 890732 (Box 373, Folder 4)
- Project Planning Guide for Powell Library, Life Safety and Rehabilitation 1975-1976 (940150)., 1974.; 890731 (Box 373, Folder 5)
- UCLA Theses and Dissertations: copyright and photocopying issues for discussion., 1978-1981.; 890730 (Box 373, Folder 6)
- Academic Senate Library Committee information packet., 1982-1983.; 890729 (Box 373, Folder 7)
- Academic Senate Library Committee., 1982-1983.; 890728 (Box 373, Folder 8)
- JRC [James R. Cox] chronological file., 1979.; 890727 (Box 373, Folder 9-21)
- JRC [James R. Cox] correspondence., 890714 (Box 373, Folder 22)
- CD2 [Collection Development]., 1970-1973.; 890713 (Box 373, Folder 23-24)
- Detailed Project Program for College Library Alterations, step 2. Los Angeles Campus., 1966.; 890712 (Box 373, Folder 25)
- UCLA University Research Library (North Campus Library) Unit 2 Detailed Project Program., 1964.; 890711 (Box 373, Folder 26)
- Collection Development Committee. Chairman's notebook., 1965-1972.; 890710 (Box 373, Folder 27-30)
- Oral History Program - Faculty Advisory Committee., 1991-1992.; 890709 (Box 374, Folder 1)
- Bork, Alfred. Schools for Tomorrow., 1990.; 890708 (Box 374, Folder 2)
- Library personnel and payroll., 1990.; 890707 (Box 374, Folder 3)
- Mount St. Mary's College., 890706 (Box 374, Folder 4)
- Native American Research Center., 1989.; 890705 (Box 374, Folder 5)
- National Library of Medicine., 1989.; 890704 (Box 374, Folder 6)
- National Endowment for the Humanities., 890703 (Box 374, Folder 7)
- Northwest Campus Quality of Student Life Task Force., 1990.; 890702 (Box 374, Folder 8)
- National Endowment for the Arts., 1989-1990.; 890701 (Box 374, Folder 9)
- Northwest Association of Schools and Colleges., 890700 (Box 374, Folder 10)
- Southern Regional Library Board., 1992-1993.; 890699 (Box 374, Folder 11)
- SRLF Operating Principles., 1988-1993.; 890698 (Box 374, Folder 12)
- Northwest Association of Schools and Colleges., 890697 (Box 374, Folder 13)
- Endowments., 1992.; 890696 (Box 374, Folder 14)
- Smoking [Research Library Policy]., 1990-1991.; 890695 (Box 374, Folder 15)
- Social Sciences computing facility., 890694 (Box 374, Folder 16)
- Graduate School of Library and information Science., 1989-1993.; 890693 (Box 374, Folder 17-19)
- Academic Council., 1991-1993.; 890692 (Box 374, Folder 20-25)
- Academic Technology Center., 1992-1993.; 890688 (Box 374, Folder 26)
- Academic Computing Council., 1989-1992.; 890687 (Box 374, Folder 27)
- Academic Computing Council. Task Force on Academic Computing., 1989-1993.; 890686 (Box 374, Folder 28-29)
- Academic Computing Council. Task Force on Academic Computing (cancelled), 1991 October; 890685 (Box 375, Folder 1-2)
- Academic Computing Planning Committee, 1992-1993; 890684 (Box 375, Folder 3-6)
- Access Services - Research Library, 1993; 890681 (Box 375, Folder 7)
- Acquisitions and gifts, 1989-1992; 890680 (Box 375, Folder 8)
- Administrative Computing Committee (ACC), 1989-1992; 890683 (Box 375, Folder 9-10)
- Administrative Information Systems, 1990-1993; 890678 (Box 375, Folder 11)
- African-American Studies, Center for, 1990-1993; 890677 (Box 375, Folder 12)
- Alumni Association, 1990-1993; 890676 (Box 375, Folder 13-14)
- American Council of Learned Societies, 1991-1992; 890674 (Box 375, Folder 15)
- American Library Association, 1992; 890673 (Box 375, Folder 16)
- Library Automation Review Committee (LARC), 1986; 890672 (Box 375, Folder 17)
- LAUC Ad Hoc Committee on Management Options, 1991-1992; 890671 (Box 375, Folder 18)
- Librarians Association UC (LAUC) Systemwide, 1981-1992; 890668 (Box 375, Folder 19-25)
- LEGI-SLATE, 1992; 890663 (Box 375, Folder 26)
- Dialog v. 1 insert [template]., n.d.; 890662 (Box 376, Folder 1)
- CIS Search Profiles., 890661 (Box 376, Folder 2)
- Requests for credit., 1976.; 890660 (Box 376, Folder 3)
- Terminals., 1976.; 890659 (Box 376, Folder 4)
- Planning document [CIS}., 890658 (Box 376, Folder 5)
- Data Services Program budget requests., 1976-1977.; 890657 (Box 376, Folder 6)
- Chancellor's Conference on Long Range Development Plan. Lake Arrowhead (held on Oct. 13-15, 1989)., 890656 (Box 376, Folder 7-8)
- Architecture and Urban Planning Library (AUPL)., 1985-1988.; 890655 (Box 376, Folder 9)
- Arts, etc. consolidations/mergers., 1991-1992.; 890654 (Box 376, Folder 10)
- Arts Library., 890653 (Box 376, Folder 11)
- Arts Library., 1992-1993.; 890652 (Box 376, Folder 12)
- Annual report samples., 1988-1990.; 890651 (Box 376, Folder 13-14)
- Association of American Universities Research Libraries Project., 1993.; 890650 (Box 376, Folder 15)
- Asian American Studies Center., 1989-1992.; 890649 (Box 376, Folder 16)
- Arts, Architecture and Urban Planning Library (AAUP)., 890648 (Box 376, Folder 17)
- Art Library., 1990-1993.; 890647 (Box 376, Folder 18)
- Bibliographers., 1989-1993.; 890646 (Box 376, Folder 19)
- Biomed., 890645 (Box 376, Folder 20)
- Bruman [includes 2 reprints]., 1989-1993.; 890644 (Box 376, Folder 21)
- California Library Networking Task Force., 1992-1993.; 890643 (Box 376, Folder 22-25)
- CIS training [on-line]., 1975-1976.; 890640 (Box 377, Folder 1)
- Graduate School of Management Planning [computer searching]., 1974.; 890639 (Box 377, Folder 2)
- Demonstration requests., 1976.; 890638 (Box 377, Folder 3)
- New York Times, current., 890637 (Box 377, Folder 4)
- Center for Information Services., 1973-1974.; 890636 (Box 377, Folder 5)
- Computerized Bibliographic Search Service., 1976.; 890635 (Box 377, Folder 6)
- Data Services: administration, planning, etc., 1975-1976.; 890634 (Box 377, Folder 7)
- Price chart 1-30 min., 1976.; 890633 (Box 377, Folder 8)
- Forms and logs - examples., 890632 (Box 377, Folder 9)
- Association of Public Data Users (APDU) Data File Directory pp 1-680., 1976.; 890631 (Box 377, Folder 10-11)
- Griffith Project (undergraduate class bibliographies)., 1976.; 890630 (Box 377, Folder 12-13)
- Computerized Bibliographic Search Service planning document 2nd draft., 1976.; 890629 (Box 377, Folder 14)
- CIS Presentations by Brokers - Documentation Associates., 1970.; 890628 (Box 377, Folder 15)
- CIS On-line Services Documentation., 1975-1976.; 890627 (Box 377, Folder 16)
- Data Services SDC/Lockheed contracts and billing information., 1975-1976.; 890626 (Box 377, Folder 17)
- DIALOG chronological summary v. 1., 1973-1974.; 890625 (Box 377, Folder 18-20)
- SDC Search Service., 1976.; 890622 (Box 377, Folder 21)
- CIS Chemical Abstracts., 890621 (Box 377, Folder 22)
- CIS SSCI SCI., 1976.; 890620 (Box 377, Folder 23)
- Stanford University Data File Directory., 1973.; 890619 (Box 377, Folder 24)
- ERIC, How to Use, slides, from Ed/Psych Library., n.d.; 890618 (Box 377, Folder 25)
- Social Sciences Citation Index slides, from Ed/Psych Library., 890617 (Box 377, Folder 26)
- Psychological Abstracts, Guide to, slides, n.d.; 890616 (Box 377, Folder 27)
- Library Automation Review Committee (LARC)., 1986; 890615 (Box 378, Folder 1-4)
- Latin American Center., 1989.; 890611 (Box 378, Folder 5)
- Law Library., 1989-1993.; 890610 (Box 378, Folder 6)
- LAUC-LA., 890609 (Box 378, Folder 7)
- Library of Congress., 1989-1992.; 890608 (Box 378, Folder 8)
- Library Information Systems., 1990-1993.; 890607 (Box 378, Folder 9)
- Library Staff Association., 890606 (Box 378, Folder 10)
- Listservs., 1992-1995.; 890605 (Box 378, Folder 11)
- Management Library., 1990-1993.; 890604 (Box 378, Folder 12)
- Map Library., 890603 (Box 378, Folder 13)
- MELVYL., 1989-1991.; 890602 (Box 378, Folder 14)
- Murphy, Franklin D., 1991; 1993.; 890601 (Box 378, Folder 15)
  Includes 75th Birthday Celebration Brochure (1993) and lecture to Grolier Club (1991).
- Music Library., 1991-1993.; 890600 (Box 378, Folder 16)
- National Endowment for the Humanities., 1981-1984.; 890599 (Box 378, Folder 17)
- NRLF., 1989-1991.; 890598 (Box 378, Folder 18)
- Office of Academic Computing., 890597 (Box 378, Folder 19)
- OCLC., 1991-1992.; 890596 (Box 378, Folder 20)
- Office of Instructional Development., 1993.; 890595 (Box 378, Folder 21)
- Office of Instructional Development (1 of 3)., 1990-1992.; 890594 (Box 378, Folder 22-24)
- Info Kiosk., 890593 (Box 378, Folder 25)
- College of Letters and Sciences. Life Sciences Division., 1989.; 890592 (Box 378, Folder 26)
- G4 (Group 4 - Cal Tech, Claremont, Occidental, Pomona) (1 of 2)., 1992-1993.; 890591 (Box 378, Folder 27-28)
- Keck Foundation proposal., 1993.; 890590 (Box 378, Folder 29)
- GSLIS (Graduate School of Library and Information Science)., 1993.; 890589 (Box 378, Folder 30)
- Annual Reports, Libraries of the University of California, 1950-1958; 1310183 (Box 379, Folder 1)
- Reports of the University Librarian to the Chancellor, 1959-1973; 1310184 (Box 379, Folder 2)
- Robert Vosper Correspondence, 1944-1969; 1310289 (Box 379, Folder 3-6)
- Lawrence Clark Powell Correspondence, 1944-c.1954; 1310291 (Box 379, Folder 7-10)
- Library Council Minutes, 1968-1976; 1310292 (Box 379, Folder 11-12)
- OCLC, 1981-1984; 1310293 (Box 379, Folder 13-14)
- Public Catalog Working Group Final Report, 1976; 1310294 (Box 379, Folder 15-16)
- Acquisitions Department, 1956-1963; 1310363 (Box 380, Folder 1)
- Acquisitions Department--"Wants" Section, c.1958-1963; 1310296 (Box 380, Folder 2)
- Senate Library Committee, 1961-1977; 1310373 (Box 380, Folder 3-5)
- Library Council Reports to University President, 1948-1974; 1310374 (Box 380, Folder 6)
- Personnel, Classifications, Rate Plans and Management Review, 1966-1976; 1310378 (Box 380, Folder 7-8)
- Data Services Coordination and CIS-Computer Information Services; Data Systems, 1974-1985; 1310380 (Box 380, Folder 9)
- New York Times Information Bank, 1975; 1310381 (Box 380, Folder 10)
- Public Services Committee, 1968-1972; 1310384 (Box 380, Folder 11-13)
- Public Catalog Working Group, 1976; 1310385 (Box 380, Folder 14)
- Library Policy Task Force, 1973-1975; 1310386 (Box 380, Folder 15)
- Acquisitions Ad Hoc Committe; Collection Development, 1973; 1983; 1310387 (Box 380, Folder 16)
- Technical Processes Committee, 1970-1971; 1310412 (Box 381, Folder 1-3)
- Dualabs. General, 1974-1975; 1310413 (Box 381, Folder 4)
- Peter Watson. Data Services, 1973-1975; 1310415 (Box 381, Folder 5)
- Association of Scientific Information Dissemination Centers ASIDiC, c.1969-1975; 1310416 (Box 381, Folder 6)
- Center for Information Services; Center for Research Libraries, 1970-1976; 1310417 (Box 381, Folder 7-10)
- Data Services, 1970s; 1310420 (Box 381, Folder 11)
- New York Times Information Bank, c.1960s-1970s; 1310422 (Box 381, Folder 12-21)
- Acquisitions; Neal Harlow Correspondence; Neal Harlow/Andrew Horn, c.1940s; 1950s; 1960s; 1311244 (Box 382, Folder 2-5)
- Institute of Industrial Relations Librarian; Lawrence Clark Powell; Paul Dodd, c. 1945-1949; 1311256 (Box 382, Folder 6)
- Ruth Gibbs; Equal Oportunity; Diversity, c.1970-1980s; 1311243 (Box 382, Folder 1)
- Acquisitions, c. 1949-1961; 1315200; Includes Neal Harlow correspondence (Box 382, Folder 2-5)
- Insitute of Industrial Relations, 1946-1949; 1315201 (Box 382, Folder 6)
- Copiers/Computers, 1311257 (Box 382, Folder 7-9)
- Library Council, c.1973-1978; 1311265 (Box 382, Folder 10-11)
- Library Service for Undergraduates; UCLA Library Space Plan; Project Planning Guide, Powell Library Building Seismic Study, 1980; 1984-1994; 1985; 1311272 (Box 382, Folder 12)
- Library Automation, 1967; 1983; 1311279 (Box 382, Folder 13)
- Intercampus Exchange Budget, 1971-1974; 1311318 (Box 382, Folder 14)
- Calinet, 1972-1978; 1311319 (Box 382, Folder 15-17)
- Intercampus Vehicle, c. 1975-1983; 1311322 (Box 382, Folder 18)
- Southern California Interlibrary Loan; Interlibrary Loan; Report of Intercampus Interlibrary Loan, c.1967-1980; 1311264 (Box 383, Folder 1-7)
- Center for Research Libraries Newsletter and Correspondence, 1968-1980; 1313136 (Box 383, Folder 8-9)
- UCLA Library Administrative Network: Evaluation Study, 1971; 1313146 (Box 383, Folder 10)
- Adminstrative Memoranda, 1966-1972; 1313142 (Box 383, Folder 11)
- Library Staff Association, 1980s; 1313143 (Box 383, Folder 12-14)
- Law Library, 1980s; 1313147 (Box 383, Folder 15)
- Norman Dudley files, 1969-1971; 1313164 (Box 384, Folder 1)
- Procedures and Analysis of Borrowing or Photocopying Journal Titles; Public Service Manuals, 1980s; 1313170 (Box 384, Folder 2)
- Administrative Information Meeting Minutes; Library Executive Advisory Committee; Report on Census and Survey of Departmental Libraries; Conditions and Limitations Amendment #12, 1980s; 1313174 (Box 384, Folder 3)
- Acquisitions Department Book Fund Reports and Statistics, 1960-1969; 1313180 (Box 384, Folder 4-5)
- Acquisitions: Correspondence relating to failed bid for Verga Collection; Jewish Research Literature Cataloguing Project Description, c.1976; 1978; 1313182 (Box 384, Folder 6)
- Cataloguing Department Budgets, 1947-1967; 1313737 (Box 384, Folder 7-12)
- North Campus Library/Young Research Library; Space Analysis and Building Program, 1957-1961; 1313876 (Box 384, Folder 13)
- Library Space Analysis and Statistics, 1964-1965; 1315062 (Box 384, Folder 14)
- William (Bill) Bergeron Building Coordinator Administrative Files; Brooke Whiting/Andrew Horn correspondence re: Library Special Collections Move from Powell Library to Research Library, Unit II, 1970-1971; 1315163 (Box 384, Folder 15)
- Research Library Unit II Space Analysis, Move, Equipment, 1963-1970; 1315190; Includes blue prints (Box 385, Folder 1-6)
- Engineering and Math Sciences (EMS) Expansion Plans and Moore Hall Addition, 1963-1972; 1315199; Includes blue prints (Box 385, Folder 5-6)
- Reference Department Interlibrary Loan Reports: Annual, Monthly and Quarterly, 1937-1977; 1315205 (Box 385, Folder 7-12)
- Intercampus Loan Analyses Term Papers, 1972/1973; 1315206 (Box 385, Folder 12)
- Bilge Collection of Turkish Books and Manuscripts Correspondence and Turkish manuscripts correspondence, 1962; 1315241 (Box 385, Folder 13)
- Information Center for Southern California Libraries., 1969-1971; 1315330 (Box 385, Folder 14)
- Acquisitions and Collection Development, 1971-1973; 1315591; Includes Newspaper Subcommittee, Collection Development Committee, Budgetary Criteria Subcommittee, the Education Subcommittee and Annual Statistics Reports of the Acquisitions Department (Box 385, Folder 15)
- Library Executive Advisory Committee, 1978-1980; 1315592 (Box 385, Folder 16)
- Library Accounting Book Fund Reports, 1973-1982; 1315203 (Box 386, Folder 1-4)
- Library Growth Plans and Projections, 1965-1980; 1315666 (Box 387, Folder 1)
- Acquisitions Department Monthly Statistics, 1962-1965; 1315667 (Box 387, Folder 2)
- Preservation Proposals; Chris[topher] Coleman correspondence, c.197-1990; 1315668 (Box 387, Folder 3)
- Health Sciences Libraries Questionnaires and Surveys, c.1977-1980; 1315670 (Box 387, Folder 4)
- Ed{ucation] Psych[ology] Library, 1971; 1983-1990; 1315671; Includes Reference Manual and Reference Survey, Barbara Duke Memoranda, Reserves, Serials Review and Cancellation, Statistics, TESL Collection (Box 387, Folder 5-10)
- Administrative Memoranda, Distribution, 1966-1975; 1315680; Includes Vosper and Ackerman memos covering Research Library Unit II, Administrative Planning, Acquisitions, Budget, Circulation, Personnel, Committee Meetings, Unified Annual Report, Physical Plant and Copy and Public Services. (Box 387, Folder 11-13)
- Network Operations Committee, 1972-1974; 1315682 (Box 387, Folder 14-15)
- Library Administrative Manual, 1952; 1315683 (Box 387, Folder 16)
- Technical Services Committee Meeting Minutes, 1969-1975; 1315684 (Box 387, Folder 17)
- Data and Information Services Coordination and Training, 1975; 1315731; Includes Peter Watson memos; New York Times Information Bank; Center for Information Services; (Box 388, Folder 1-2)
- Collection Development Committee, 1975; 1315908 (Box 388, Folder 3)
- Committee on Committees, 1970-1971; 1315909 (Box 388, Folder 4)
- Staff Resources Committee, 1970-1972; 1315910 (Box 388, Folder 5)
- Public Services, 1968-1974; 1987; 1988; 1992/1993; 1315911; Includes Committee Meetings, Manual and Addenda, Statistics and Workload Statistics (Box 388, Folder 6-13)
- Physics Library, 1968-1985; 1315929; From the administrative files of J. Wally Pegram, Physics Librarian 1971-1991 includes Unit Heads Memos, budget and statistics information, book allocation information and miscellaneous files (Box 388, Folder 14-18)
- Annual Report Summaries, 1983-1984; 1316092 (Box 388, Folder 19)
- Art Library. NEH Grant Proposal: Catalog Belt Vinciana, 1983; 1316093 (Box 388, Folder 20)
- No Box 389-397
- Academic Communication Facility, 1967, 1971; 1435579; 1 folders (Box 398, Folder 1)
- Acquisitions, 1966-1969; 1435593 (Box 398, Folder 2)
- Building East Wing Addition, 1946-1948; 1435585 (Box 398, Folder 3)
- Education Psychology Annual Reports, 1975-1981; 1435842; 2 folders (Box 398, Folder 4-5)
- Education Psychology Library Closure/Merger, 1991; 1435838; 2 folders (Box 398, Folder 6-7)
- Education Psychology Procedures Manuals, 1985, 1991; 1435840 (Box 398, Folder 8)
- Finishes, 1969; 1435595 (Box 398, Folder 9)